What's on your shopping list,
or if you have some starting index, then
look at Vrindavan. I
think the gap is going to give you
money today because of tomorrow's holiday. And
look at Bank Nifty, two, almost 15018 points have been
collected. And double no, this
lifting of oil prices is always there.
I think the surprise entry will be
from the family tree. Bank will sleep 512, and bank
charges disclosure, and 10,000
opportunities to buy. If you are
seeing so much strain in the cement seal now, then
credit the story. The credit cycle
store in launch. And there is no reason why one should not
report solid numbers
starting with ICICI Bank and
followed by SBI Axis. And so
both my trends are going towards lending and a
mortgage institution. And I would
also say that this thickness in Bank Nifty is not surprising.
Refer to Monday and expiry on Thursday.  If
any alarm point is found above this day, then the
time lighting market is so high that it is believed to be
oversold, so much start is happening in Bank Nifty
that it is trading at a discount,
wear the best top,
stoploss at HDFC 2465 and
target of 2410 2565, 40.50 600 ₹40,
ICICI Bank collapsed in Thane, stoploss of Khusro 21,
target of 665